Turkus, Burton B. Arbitration Files 5712
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- British Airways vs. IAM, District Lodge 100, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  2/5/79. Issue: Insubordination - failure to obey orders. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, Union brief, correspondence, supporting documentation
- British Airways vs. IAM, District Lodge 100, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  1/23/78. Issue: Absences - excessive. Includes: Agreement, Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation, Employees' memorandum
- British Airways vs. IAM, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  9/10/73. Issue: Overtime - emergency assignment.
- British Airways vs. IAM, District Lodge 100, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  7/23/69. Issue: Promotions - seniority.
- British Airways vs. IAM, District Lodge 100, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  7/31/69. Issue: Promotions - seniority.
- British Airways vs. IAM, District Lodge 100, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  3/30/77. Issue: withdrawn
- British Airways vs. IAM, District Lodge 100, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  5/23/50. Issue: Classification of jobs - assignment of work outside classification. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, Agreement
- British Airways vs. IAM, District Lodge 100, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  3/27/80. Issue: withdrawn
- Brook Club vs. HMCEBU, Local 6, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  4/10/79. Issue: withdrawn
- Brooke Bond Foods, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 202, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  12/17/76. Issue: withdrawn
- Brooklyn Dressing Corporation vs. Fur Floor Workers Union, Local 3F, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  3/23/76. Issue: Absences - excessive excused absences. Includes: Correspondence
- Brooklyn Dressing Corporation vs. Fur Floor Workers Union, Local 3F, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  3/23/76. Issue: Absences - excessive excused absences. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation, Arbitrator's notes, Agreement.
- Brooklyn Hospital vs. SEIU, Local 144, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  7/15/81. Issue: Dismissal - withdrawn. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, stipulation
- Brooklyn Hospital vs. SEIU, Local 144, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  4/25/80? Issue: Welfare funds - Employer contribution. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, proceeding transcripts. No Award.
- Building Contractors Association, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 282, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  6/18/79. Issue: Seniority - waiver of seniority. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, Company brief, Union brief, Agreement.
- Burns International Security Services vs. IUPPE-ILWA, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  1/30/78. Issue: withdrawn.
- Butler Aviation, Boston, Inc. vs. IAM, Lodge 141, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  11/11/75. Issue: Discipline - discharge.
- Calmar, Inc. vs. IAM, District Lodge 61, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  7/30/68. Issue: Union representatives and business - discipline.
- Canada Dry Corporation vs. OPEIU, Local 153, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  4/20/70. Issue: Negotiations - Arbitration procedure.
- Capital City Products Company vs. ILA, Local 996, Lighter Captains Union, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  11/16/75. Issue: Vacancies - transfers. Includes: Correspondence, Arbitrator's notes, Agreement
- Carey Cadillac Venting Company, Inc. vs. IAMAW, District 15, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  3/31/80. Issue: withdrawn.
- Castaways Motel vs. Hotel, Motel, Restaurant and High-Rise Employees and Bartenders Union, Local 355, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  11/25/74. Issue: Improper personal conduct - standards of conduct.
- Central Hudson Gas and Electric Corporation vs. IBEW, Local 320, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  5/8/79. Issue: Discipline - refusal to return to work. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, Employer's brief, Union brief, photographs and supporting documentation
- Cerro Wire and Cable Company vs. IBT, Local 1922, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  9/16/75. Issue: Discipline - accident-proneness.
- Chandler Evans, Inc. vs. UAW, Unity Lodge 405, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  2/24/72. Issue: Transfers - involuntary
- Charro Trucking Corporation vs. IBT Local 202, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  7/8/82. Issue: Welfare funds - Employer's contribution. Includes: Correspondence
- Cheshire Cat vs. HREBU, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  1/8/81. Issue: Discipline - discharge; Arbitrability - jurisdiction. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation, Union post-hearing brief, Agreement.
- Chrysler Corporation vs. IBT, Local 868, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  11/20/81. Issue: withdrawn
- Cinema Television Design vs. IATSE, Local 841, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  12/15/80. Issue: Vacation pay - computation. Includes: Correspondence
- Coastal Dry Dock and Repair Corporation vs. IUMSWA, Local 12, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  2/27/82. Issue: Improper personal conduct - detrimental conduct. Includes: Agreement, correspondence, Employer's and Union briefs
- Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. vs. IBEW, Local 1212, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  11/22/77. Issue: Improper job attitude - general attitude Includes: Correspondence, Arbitrator's notes, supporting documentation
- Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. vs. IBEW, Local 1212, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  2/11/80. Issue: Discipline - discharge.
- Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. vs. IBEW, Local 1212, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  2/16/78. Issue: Severance pay - management obligation to pay Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. vs. IBEW, Local 1212, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  1/26/79 Issue: Discipline - discharge. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence
- Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. vs. United Piano Workers Union, Local 102, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  5/18/81. Issue: withdrawn
- Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. vs. IATSE, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  5/15/80. Issue: Recall - failure to recall. Includes: Agreement, correspondence, supporting documentation, transcript of Arbitration hearing
- Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. vs. IBEW, Local 1212, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  6/4/80. Issue: withdrawn.
- Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. vs. IBEW, Local 1212, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  7/24/79. Issue: Absences - discipline. Includes: Correspondence, Company brief, supporting documentation, Arbitrator's notes, Agreement
- Columbia Pictures vs. Directors' Guild of America, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  3/29/79. No Award
- Columbus Hospital vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, Local 1199, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  9/15/76. Issue: Improper personal conduct - theft. Includes: Agreement, correspondence
- Commerce Labor Industry, Corporation of Things vs. IBT, Local 803, Security Guards and Watchmen's Union, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  4/12/79. Issue: Improper personal conduct - unauthorized use of Company property. Includes: Union brief, supporting documentation, Arbitrator's notes, Company brief, Agreement.
- Community Board of Martin Luther King Health Center vs. New York State Federation of Physicians and Dentists, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  5/24/79. Issue: withdrawn
- Concourse Nursing Home vs. Hotel, Hospital, Nursing Home and Allied Health Services Union, Local 144, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  8/2/80. Includes: 3 United States District Court decisions. No Award
- Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc. vs. Utility Workers Union of America, Local 1-2, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  10/3/73. Issue: Improper personal conduct - interference with production. Includes: Prior Arbitration record.
- Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc. vs. IBEW, Local 3, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  1/6/76. Issue: Theft - Company product Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation
- Consolidated Fine Housekeeping, Inc. vs. Nursing Home and Hospital Employees Division, Local 1115, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  3/18/76. Issue: Card check and count. Includes: Supporting documentation
- Constitution Realty Corporation vs. SEIU, Local 325, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  1/21/77. Issue: Rates of pay - workload.
- Continental Airlines, Inc. vs. Airline Pilots Association International, Association of Flight Attendants, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  1/31/75. Issue: Absences - discipline. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation, United States District Court decisions, financial records.
- Cook Machinery Company vs. IUE, Local 438, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  12/14/67. Issue: Coffee breaks - plant rules.
- Courier-Citizen Company vs. Lowell Printing and Graphic Communications Union, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  6/3/77. Issue: Improper personal conduct - interference with production Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation
- C.W. Post College vs. SEIU, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  8/17/71. Issue: Strikes, slowdowns, and work stoppages - Wildcat strikes.
- Davis and Fisher Machine Company vs. USA, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  6/22/79. Issue: withdrawn
- Deauville Hotel vs. Hotel, Motel, Restaurant and High-Rise Employees and Bartenders Union, Local 355, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  7/9/75. Issue: Improper job attitude - general attitude; sleeping on job.
- Delta Steamship Lines, Inc. vs. International Organization of Masters, Mates, and Pilots, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  1/4/82. Issue: Rates of pay - differential in pay. Includes: Agreement, correspondence, Company and Union briefs
- DJA Enterprises, Inc. vs. Hotel, Motel, Restaurant and High-Rise Employees and Bartenders Union, Local 355, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  6/10/75. Issue: Assignment of job - change of duty.
- DMC Company vs. IAMAW, Lodge 15, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  7/25/80. Issue: Call-in - Acts of God. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation
- Dobbs House, Inc. vs. Hotel, Motel, Restaurant and High-Rise Employees and Bartenders Union, Local 355, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  11/17/75. Issue: Improper personal conduct - standards of conduct. Includes: Correspondence
- Doral County Club vs. Hotel, Motel, Restaurant and High-Rise Employees and Bartenders Union, Local 355, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  9/2/75. Issue: Discipline - discharge.
- Dovar Shipping Agency, Inc. vs. OPEIU, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  8/30/71. Issue: Absences - discipline.
- Dow Jones and Company, Inc. vs. Independent Association of Publishers Employees, Inc, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  11/3/76. Issue: Overtime - failure to schedule. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation
- Drakes Bakery, Wayne, New Jersey vs. Bakery and Confectionery Workers Union, Local 50, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  5/22/75. Issue: Seniority - bumping
- Dupont Plaza Hotel vs. Hotel, Motel, Restaurant and High-Rise Employees and Bartenders Union, Local 355, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  9/16/74 Issue: Improper personal conduct - disruptive influence.
- Duval Sierrita Corporation vs. IBT, Local 310, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  5/26/76. Issue: withdrawn
- Eagle Electric Manufacturing Company vs. UAW, Local 365, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  1/5/78/ Issue: settled.
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. IAMAW, Lodge 100, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  9/28/73. Issue: withdrawn
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. IAMAW, Lodge 100, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  6/8/77. Issue: Classification of job - assignment of work outside classification. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. IAMAW, Lodge 101, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  7/3/80. Issue: Improper job attitude - conspiracy. Includes: Transcript, correspondence, Arbitrator's notes, supporting documentation
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. Eastern Airlines Steward and Stewardesses Association, Local 553, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  4/3/80. Issue: Alcoholism, drinking and intoxication - Burden of proof. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation, previous case awards, medical reports
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. Air Transport Division, Local 553, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  9/22/80. Issue: Theft - pilfering. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, agenda, correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. Air Transport Division, Local 553, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  4/30/81. Issue: Detrimental conduct (drug use). Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, financial receipts, supporting documentation, transcript of testimony
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. Eastern Airlines Steward and Stewardesses Association, Local 553, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  9/29/80. Issue: Detrimental conduct (drug use). Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation, partial transcript of testimony.
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. IAMAW, District Lodge 100, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  6/7/77. Issue: Strikes, slowdowns, and work stoppages - work stoppages. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, post-hearing briefs.
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. IAMAW, District 100, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  4/6/81. Issue: Vacancies - method of filling. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation, prior cases.
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. Eastern Airlines Steward and Stewardesses Association, Air Transport Division Local 553, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  4/3/80. Issue: Quits - notice of intent. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence.
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. Eastern Airlines Steward and Stewardesses Association, Air Transport Division Local 553, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  2/4/80. Issue: Alcoholism, drinking, and intoxication - drinking prior to reporting. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation, post-hearing statement.
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. IAM, District Lodge 100, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  3/15/68. Issue: Classification of jobs - assignment defined.
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs Eastern Airlines Steward and Stewardesses Association, Transport Workers Air Transport Division, Local 553, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  5/15/79. Issue: Alcoholism, drinking and intoxication - drinking prior to reporting. Includes: Arbitrator's notes.
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. IAMAW, District 100, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  6/11/79. Issue: Theft - Company property. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. Eastern Airlines Steward and Stewardesses Association, Transport Workers Air Transport Division, Local 553, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  5/25/79. Issue: Alcoholism, drinking and intoxication - events subsequent to discharge. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation, transcript.
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. IAMAW, District 100, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  5/31/79. Issue: Theft - Company property. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, post-hearing Union brief, post-hearing Employer brief.
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. IAMAW, District Lodge 100, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  12/26/78. Issue: Improper personal conduct - conviction of crime. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. Eastern Airlines Steward and Stewardesses Association, Transport Workers Air Transport Division, Local 553 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Not dated. Issue: Alcoholism, drinking and intoxication - drinking on the job. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation, post-hearing Employer brief.
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. IAMAW, District Lodge 100, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  6/7/79. Issue: Alcoholism, drinking and intoxication - evidence. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation, Union post-hearing brief, Company post-hearing brief.
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. IAMAW, District Lodge 100, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  8/20/79. Issue: Alcohol, drinking and intoxication - drinking on the job. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation, transcript of proceedings.
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. Eastern Airlines Steward and Stewardesses Association, Transport Workers Air Transport Division, Local 553, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  12/27/78. Issue: Absences - excessive. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. IAMAW, District 100, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  12/26/78. Issue: Theft - Company property. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, financial transcripts, supporting documentation, correspondence.
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. IAMAW, District 100, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  1/17/78. Issue: withdrawn.
- Eastern Greyhound Lines vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, CLC, Division 1202 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Not dated. Issue: Strikes, slowdowns, and work stoppages - discipline.
- Ecuatoriana vs. IAMAW, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  7/3/79. Issue: withdrawn
- Eden Roc Hotel vs. HMRHREBU, Local 355, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  5/30/75. Issue: Welfare funds - Employer's contribution.
- El Al Israel Airlines vs. IAMAW, District 100, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  8/7/80. Issue: Improper job attitude - general attitude. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation, supporting case.
- El Al Israel Airlines vs. IAMAW, District 100, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  6/15/82. Issue: Vacancies - posting. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence
- Elevator Manufacturers' Association of New York vs. International Union of Elevator Constructors, Local 1, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  1/22/71. Issue: Management rights - Time-off schedules (Bomb threats).
- Elevator Manufacturers' Association of New York vs. International Union of Elevator Constructors, Local 1, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  10/18/71. Issue: Strikes, slowdowns, and work stoppages - work stoppage.
- Elevator Manufacturers' Association of New York vs. International Union of Elevator Constructors, Local 1, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  1/22/71. Issue: Vacations - computation.
- Elizabeth Arden Sales Corporation vs. OCAW, Local 8-149, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  8/15/68. Issue: Absences - discipline.
- Emery Air Freight Corporation vs. IBT, Local 851, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  3/11/76. Issue: withdrawn.
- Endo Laboratories, Inc. vs. SEIU, Local 100, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  11/26/75. Issue: Past practice - travel pay. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation, Company brief, Union memoranda
- Engelhard Industries vs. UAW, Local 1668, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  7/1/81. Issue: withdrawn
- Enterprise Publishing Company vs. Newspaper Guild of Brookton, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  9/15/80. Issue: withdrawn
- Ethyl Corporation vs. IAMAW, District 15, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  2/21/78. Issue: withdrawn
- Everglades Hotel vs. HREBU, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  8/8/73. Issue: Improper personal conduct - indecent conduct.
- F&M Schaefer Brewing Company vs. OPEIU, Local 153, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  10/5/71. Issue: Improper job attitude - general attitude.
- F&M Schaefer Brewing Company vs. OPEIU, Local 153, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  7/21/75. Issue: Discipline - negligence and carelessness.
- Falcon Jet Corporation vs. Transport Workers, Local 509, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  5/9/77. Issue: withdrawn. Includes: Agreement, correspondence.
- Farrell Lines, Inc. vs. NMU, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  2/21/79. Issue: Hiring - temporary employees. Includes: Correspondence.
- Farrell Lines, Inc. vs. NMU, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  1/18/79. Issue: Improper personal conduct - detrimental conduct. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation, Company brief, Union brief
- Firestone Tire and Rubber Company vs. IBT, Local 917, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  12/1/78. Issue: Arbitration procedure - delay in arbitration Award.
- First National Stores, Inc. vs. Retail Clerks International Association, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  2/24/81. Issue: withdrawn
- First National Supermarkets vs. FBT, Local 559, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  4/13/82. Issue: withdrawn.
- Flatbush Manor, C.C. vs. Nursing Home and Hospital Employees Union, Joint Board 1115, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  8/11/82. Issue: Card check and count
- Florida Power Corporation vs. IBEW, System Council U-8, Local 682, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  5/5/75. Issue: Insubordination - plant rules in general
- FMC Corporation, Drive Division vs. USA, Local 3828 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Not dated. Issue: Absences - discipline. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation, Agreement.
- Fontainebleau Hotel vs. HMREBU, Local 355, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  8/25/75. Issue: Bargaining unit - Employees within bargaining unit. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Fontainebleau Hotel vs. HMREBU, Local 356, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  1/15/76. Issue: Discipline - discharge.
- Food Fair Stores, Inc. vs. Retail Clerks International Association, Local 1500, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  6/27/78. Issue: Improper job attitude - insubordination. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence.
- Foreign Tours vs. IAMAW, District 100, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  2/23/82. Issue: withdrawn
- Friedland Wine and Liquor vs. Wine and Liquor Store Employees Union, Local 122, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  3/31/80. Issue: Lie Detector Tests - refusal to take, effect. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, supporting documentation, Agreement
- Frito-Lay, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 802, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  12/2/75. Issue: withdrawn
- GAF Corporation vs. IBT, Local 445, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  4/18/77. Issue: Hours of work, seniority. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, Agreement, supporting documentation.
- GAL 57/58 Gourmet, Ltd. vs. Culinary Employees Union, Division of 1115 Joint Board, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 17a)
  8/9/82. Issue: Union representation - certification. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, exhibits, correspondence, legal documents.
- Gallagher's Steak House vs. HREIU, Local 69, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  6/25/79. Issue: Discipline - dishonesty. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, Arbitrator's notes
- Gaslight Club, Inc. vs. Dining Room Employees, Local 1, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  6/14/78. Issue: Discharge - mode of dress. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, exhibits.
- Gaslight Club, Inc. vs. Dining Room Employees, Local 1, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  9/15/78. Issue: Discipline - discharge - working rules. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, supporting documentation.
- General Dynamics vs. Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers, Local 90, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  1/23/76. Issue: Assignment of jobs - recall. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, exhibits, briefs, supporting documentation, correspondence.
- General Dynamics vs. IUMSW, Local 5, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  7/6/76. Issue: Recall - seniority. Includes: Briefs, correspondence.
- General Dynamics vs. IUMSW, Local 5, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  8/16/76. Issue: Discipline - discharge; Application for employment - falsification. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation, legal documents.
- General Dynamics vs. IUMSW, Local 5, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  7/7/76. Issue: Discipline - discharge; Absences; Alcoholism; Threats. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, legal documents.
- General Dynamics vs. IUMSW, Local 90, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  8/22/78. Issue: Discipline - discharge; Assignment of job; Insubordination. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- General Dynamics vs. IUMSW, Local 5, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  5/30/80. Issue: withdrawn
- General Dynamics vs. IUMSW, Local 90, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  5/7/79. Issue: Layoff - recall. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, legal documents, briefs, exhibits.
- General Dynamics vs. IBEW, Local 3, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  9/17/79. Issue: Discipline - discharge - dishonesty.
- General Telephone Company of Florida vs. IBEW, Local 824, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 28a)
  4/5/74. Issue: Safety - plant rules. Includes: Award only.
- General Tire and Rubber Company vs. IBT, Local 892, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 28b)
  4/11/73. Issue: Strikes - wildcat strikes. Includes: Award only.
- Gentry International vs. OCAW, Local 8-712 (Box 8, Folder 28c)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - dishonesty. Includes: Award only.
- Gimbels vs. RWDSU, United Storeworkers, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  12/17/80. Issue: Discipline - discharge - plant rules. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, legal documents.